You better believe I got tricks up my sleeve
你最好相信 我~身藏绝计
And I captivate 'cause I'm powerful and grea-ea-eat
我魅力不菲 因我全能卓伟~~
Oh, whoa, oh-oh-oh-oh
You better believe I got tricks up my sleeve
你最好相信 我~身藏绝计
See me dominate, 'cause I'm powerful and grea-ea-eat
赛场我支配, 因我全能卓伟~~
Oh, whoa, oh-oh-oh-oh
You think you've got what it takes to go toe to toe?
你以为够格成为我对手?
I've got more moves than you'll ever know
我有更多招数没有楼
I own the stage, I'm all the rage
我独霸舞台, 风靡电台
You're from the past, I'm from the Space Age
你已过时, 而我超越时代
Come on, you're just making noise
拜托, 你在制造噪音
Listen how my music destroys
听我音乐如何动听
Anything you throw at me
不管你用什么武器
I'm gonna throw back, just wait and see-ee
我都会报仇, 立刻回击~
You better believe I got tricks up my sleeve
你最好相信 我~身藏绝计
And I captivate 'cause I'm powerful and grea-ea-eat
我魅力不菲 因我全能卓伟~~
Oh, whoa, oh-oh-oh-oh
You better believe I got tricks up my sleeve
你最好相信 我~身藏绝技
See me dominate, 'cause I'm powerful and grea-ea-eat
赛场我支配 因我全能卓伟~~
I'm here to take you down a peg
你面对我威风全灭
Oh, whoa, oh-whoa-oh-whoa-oh-oh
By the time I'm done, you're gonna beg
等我演奏完，你会胆怯
Oh, whoa, oh-whoa-oh-whoa-oh-oh
To be in my band, application rejected!
加入我并肩？不了谢谢！
Rejected!
不谢!
Don't look so sad and so dejected
不要黑脸，也不要呜咽
And so dejected
不要呜咽
Don't mean to brag, don't mean to boast
无需自吹，无需夸口
But I'm a six-course meal and you're just burnt toast
我是奢华大餐而你是面包头
Think I'm gonna ever give up?
以为我会中途屈服？
No, never, ever, ever, ever!
不，绝不，绝不，绝不，绝不！
Come on, you're just making noise
拜托，你在制造噪音
Listen how my music destroys
听我音乐如何动听
Anything you throw at me
不管你用什么武器
I'm gonna throw back, just wait and see-ee
我都会报仇，立刻回击~~
You better believe I got tricks up my sleeve
你最好相信 我~身藏绝技
And I captivate 'cause I'm powerful and grea-ea-eat
我魅力不菲 因我全能卓伟~~
Oh, whoa, oh-oh-oh
You better believe I got tricks up my sleeve
你最好相信 我~身藏绝技
See me dominate, 'cause I'm powerful and grea-ea-eat
赛场我支配 因我全能卓伟——！